http://www.autoextremist.com/privacy-policy/

Follow Autoextremist
Privacy PolicyAutoextremist is committed to protecting the personal information you choose to share with us. Below is our privacy guarantee and some additional information about how we gather information about our registered users, why we gather it, and what we do with it.We will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any outside source without your express consent.General informationFrom time to time, we may send to your web browser advertisements you will see when you use our network of Web sites. However, we may also allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our web pages. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad network Web site, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as if you had requested a web page from the site. Please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that ad, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. As always remember, we only authorize our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. Our third-party ad servers do not collect, nor do we give them access, to any personally identifying information about you.Opting out of third-party ad serversAlthough most Autoextremist customers indicate that they welcome details of offers and other promotional material about Autoextremist products and services and products and services provided by our business partners and advertisers, we acknowledge the right of our customers to choose. You will be given the right to opt-out of receiving such information whenever you are asked to provide information on this site. If you do not opt-out at that time, but later decide that you do not wish to receive future communications of this nature you can contact us as set out below, indicating that you no longer want to receive: (1) information relating to products and services provided by other companies, or (2) any information relating to products and services (including Autoextremist products and services).If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network’s Web site individually and opt out (if they offer this capability).Forum and message boardsThis site may make forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information in order to use these areas but you may choose to do so. Please remember that any information that you choose to disclose in these areas will be publicly available; thus, you should exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose personal information. Autoextremist cannot accept any responsibility for ensuring the privacy of information that you choose to disclose in these areas.SecurityThis site incorporates appropriate safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information we have collected and we have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss, misuse and alteration. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide us.External LinksAutoextremist provides links to various Web sites that we do not control as well as to our sponsors. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our Web site and connected to the Web site of the organization or company that you selected. Even if an affiliation exists between our Web site and a third-party Web site, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a Web site that is linked to our site, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information.
RANTS
|
ON THE TABLE
|
FUMES
|
THE LINE
|
READER MAIL
THE UNAUTHORIZED USE OF ANY EDITORIAL OR PHOTOGRAPHIC CONTENT FROM AUTOEXTREMIST.COM WITHOUT WRITTEN PERMISSION FROM THE PUBLISHER IS STRICTLY PROHIBITED.
Copyright Statement ~ © 1999-2019 Autoextremist.com, Inc. ~ Privacy Policy
